It's time to confront your demons.
Psych:9 is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Andrew Shortell.
A young woman with a troubled past takes a job at recently closed down hospital.
Working the night shift alone she begins to experience a series of unsettling events that lead her to
believe that the hospital may be connected to a number of recent murders in the area.
To uncover the truth she will have to revisit the
past behind the walls of Psych:9.
Roslyn, played by Sara Foster.
Dr. Clement, played by Cary Elwes.
Det. Marling, played by Michael Biehn.
Cole, played by Gabriel Mann.
Beth, played by Colleen Camp.
Emma, played by Winter Ave Zoli.
Psych: 9 is a 2010 American-Czech horror film directed by Andrew Shortell.
It stars Sara Foster and Michael Biehn.
The film explores themes of night shift, nurse, murder, hospital, troubled past.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.